-嗨  -嘿
-Hi.  -Hey.
这个小芭蕾舞演员是谁啊
Who is <i>this</i> little ballerina?
她是查莉  你的第四个也是最后的孩子  没错吧
It's Charlie, your fourth and <i>final</i> child, right?
那衣服简直可爱极了
Isn't that dress adorable?
这是我为她的第一堂芭蕾课买的
I bought it for her first ballet class,
而你要带她去上课  因为我明天得工作
which you are taking her to, because I have to work tomorrow.
可是  亲爱的  我本来要...我乐意之至
But, honey, I'm supposed to... I'd be happy to.
你得用录像记录下这整个过程
And I need you to videotape it,
-因为课上的细节我可不想放过  -可是摄像机
- because I don't want to miss a thing.  - But the camera I...
我乐意之至
I'd be happy to.
芭蕾  多么愚蠢的事啊
Ballet... what a stupid thing to do.
事实上  你爸爸上中学的时候也学了芭蕾
Actually, your father took ballet in High School.
太棒了
Great.
又是个让我夜不能寐的形象啊
Another image to keep me up at night.
其实  我的橄榄球球教练认为学芭蕾
Actually, our football coach thought that taking ballet
有助于我们提高身体的敏捷度和平衡能力
would help our agility and balance.
要不然他就是在忽悠我们呢
Either that or he was just really messing with us.
你应该看看你爸爸穿紧身衣的样子  一个帅哥呢
You should've seen your dad in his tights.He looked hot.
好吧  “帅”这个字
Yeah, the whole idea of "hot"
在你们那个年代一定有别的意思
must've been different in the olden days.
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
■
翻译： coala1234
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
■
校订： line
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第九集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E09  Teddy's Bear
-派珀先生  我能和你说...  -等等
-Mr. Piper, can I talk to you...  -Hold on.
-听着...  -别急
-See...  -Ah!
是什么事
Now what is it?
嗯  你听到这个一定会会心一笑的
Oh, well, you're gonna laugh when you hear this,
但是你的确犯了一个错误
but you actually made a mistake.
此时你应该会心一笑才对的
So this is where you'd be laughing.
不管怎样
Anyways, um,
看  这里的这个答案  您给我判错了
see, this answer here? You marked it wrong.
-它就是错的  -可是正确答案就是B
-It is wrong. -But the correct answer is b.
是的  但B的选项旁边的答题框你没有填涂满
Yes, but you did not completely shade in the oval next to the b,
所以你就是错了
so it is wrong.
你在开玩笑  是吗
You're kidding, right?
邓肯小姐  自打那件事以来...
Miss Duncan, I haven't kidded since...
我还真没开过玩笑
I've never kidded.
了解了
Good to know.
所以你会改了我的分数  是吗
So you're gonna change my grade, right?
-不  我不会  -可是那不公平
-No, I'm not.  -But that's not fair.
但我已经在“我不管”选项旁边的
This is me completely shading in
椭圆答题框里填涂好了
the oval next to "I don't care."
嗯
Hmm?
她在这儿  恋爱一周纪念日快乐
There she is. Happy one-week-aversary.
哦  PJ  你还记得
Oh, P.J., you remembered.
是的  还有人说我们肯定爱情持久不了呢
Yeah, and they said it wouldn't last.
还有人这么说  他们是谁
They did? Who are they?
没有谁  只是一种说辞而已
No, it's just an expression.
能和聪明人一起约会实在是太有趣了啊
Wow. It's so fun going out with a smart guy.
-我给你写了首诗  -让我看看
-I wrote a poem for you.  -Oh, let me see.
P代表你弹吉他的样子
"P is for the way you play guitar,
J代表着你讲的笑话
j is for the jokes you tell."
太优美了
Oh, that's beautiful.
是的  让句子押韵挺难的
Yeah, the hard part was getting it to rhyme,
所以我就不写了
so I didn't.
哦  我也有个礼物给你
Oh oh, I have a gift for you too.
-一条项链  -是的
-A necklace?  -Yeah.
-这是什么  -是根油条
-What's this?  -It's a piece of churro.
是我们第一次分享的甜食的最后一口
It is the last bite of the first snack we ever shared.
我真高兴
Oh, that makes me so happy.
现在我很难过
Now I'm sad.
怎么了
What's wrong?
PJ  你真了解我
Oh, P.J.,you know me so well.
确实有事发生了
Something <i>is</i> wrong.
我的前男友一直给我发短信  他想破镜重圆
My ex-boyfriend keeps texting me.He wants to get back together.
你现在戴着我的油条  关系已经如此紧密了
You're wearing my churro.We're at the churro stage.
我会和这个家伙谈谈
Well, I'll talk to this guy,
-向他直接挑明我们的关系  -真的吗
-set him straight.  -Would you?
-是的  他是谁  -他叫布洛克
-Yeah. Who is he?  -His name's brock
他是摔跤队的队长
and he's Captain of the wrestling team.
因为鲜有人击败他  所以他觉得自己很无敌
He thinks he's so great just 'cause he's undefeated.
啊  就是说他打架从没输过
Huh. So he's never lost a fight
而我从没打过架
and I've never been in a fight.
啊  这回可谈的东西好多好多啊
Huh. We should have lots to talk about.
再见
See ya.
伙计  油条阶段还真是难搞啊
Man, the churro stage is complicated.
-你好  -嗨
-Hello.  -Hi.
妈妈  能请你在这上面签个字吗
Mom, could you sign this, please?
-当然  亲爱的  -等一等
-Sure, honey.  -Wait a second.
那个动作我很清楚  她在瞒着什么事
I know that move. She's hiding something.
-不  我没有  -那就把你的手拿开
-No, I'm not.  -Then move your hand away.
人家不愿意啊
I don't <i>want</i> to.
是惩罚通知
A disciplinary notice?
是的  我就知道
Yes! I knew it!
完美小姐终于捅娄子了
Finally little miss perfect did something bad.
泰迪亲爱的  你做了什么
Okay, Teddy honey, what did you do?
什么  我什么也没做  只是惹老师生气了
What? Nothing.I just got mad at a teacher
因为我没在一个破椭圆答题框填涂好  就扣了我的分数
because he lowered my grade for not filling in a stupid oval,
所以我就拗断了他的一只破铅笔
so I snapped one of his stupid pencils.
仅此而已嘛
That's it?
我苦苦等待一生  只得到这个玩意嘛
I've waited my whole life for <i>that?</i>
泰迪亲爱的  我没听出来你做错了什么
Teddy honey, I'm not hearing that you did anything <i>wrong.</i>
因为我本来就没做错什么
Well, that's because I didn't.
好吧  看来老娘我要亲自出动
Okay, I'll tell you what...maybe I should go down
去会会那个老师了
and have a little talk with this guy.
-不不不  千万别  -为什么不
-Oh, no no no, please don't.  -Why not?
因为  一旦你和这类事情扯上关联
Well, because whenever you get involved
你就会变身成为
in stuff like this, you turn into...
-你想说暴走熊妈妈吗  -嗯
-mama bear?  -Mm-hmm.
你就担心这个吗
Is that what you're worried about?
是的
Yes.
因为只要暴走熊妈妈出洞
Because whenever mama bear comes out of her cave,
坏事就接二连三地发生
bad things happen.
没错啊  但通常我就有好戏看了
Yeah, but they're usually entertaining.
泰迪亲爱的  我绝对可以做到去学校
Teddy honey, I am more than capable of going down there
和老师冷静地讨论正经问题
and having a civilized discussion.
那么这个老师是谁
Now who is this teacher?
派珀先生
Mr. Piper.
派珀  不出所料
Ah. Piper. It figures.
没错  他也教过PJ  在PJ明显该拿D减的时候
Yeah, P.J. Had him. Gave him an f
-却给了他F  -哦
-when he clearly deserved a d-.  -Ooh.
能不能保证你不会插手此事
Can you please just promise me you won't get involved?
好吧  如果这对你很重要  我会袖手旁观的
Okay, if it's that important to you, I'll stay out of it.
暴走熊妈妈要去冬眠了
Mama bear is going into hibernation.
该死  她忘了签这个
Oh great, she forgot to sign this.
给我吧  我来帮她签上  她的签名我学的炉火纯青
Here, let me have it. I've got her signature down.
好的  加油  查莉
<i>Okay.</i> <i> Come on, Charlie.</i>
加油  旋转  旋转
<i>Come on.</i><i>Spin.</i> <i> Spin.</i>
加油  转个圈
<i>Come on,</i><i>twirl around.</i>
做个可爱的动作
<i>Well, do something cute.</i>
所以说我们要上这堂课
And that's why we need the lessons.
大家  大家
People.People.
欢迎来到唐娜小姐的芭蕾学校
Welcome to miss Donna's school of ballet.
我是唐娜小姐  我激情洋溢
I'm miss Donna, and I am <i>passionate</i>
想要把芭蕾这门艺术
about teaching the art of ballet
传授给下一代的芭蕾舞蹈演员们
to the next generation of ballerinas.
你们都付过学费了吗
Did I get everyone's check?
很好  现在魔法可以开始了
Very good. Now so the <i>magic</i> can begin,
家长可以到外面的走廊上去吗
will the parents please exit to the hallway?
还有不要从窗子里偷看
And there's no peeking in the window.
那会让孩子们分心的
It distracts the children.
嗯  唐娜小姐
Um, um, mi... miss Donna?
-什么事  -嗨  我是鲍伯·邓肯
-Yes?  -Hi, Bob Duncan.
你看  我答应了我妻子要把这堂课录下来
Listen, I promised my wife I'd videotape the class.
我还说我很确定壮汉拿摄像机
Well, I'm sure a giant man
拍来拍去不会让孩子们分心呢
with a shiny camera won't distract the children.
好吧  看  如果我不把全过程录下来的话
Okay, look, if I don't get this on tape,
我会遇到大麻烦的
I'm in really big trouble.
你惧内可不是我的问题
It's not my problem you're afraid of your wife.
拜托  我可不惧内
Okay, I am not afraid.
我只是宰相肚里能撑船
I just have a very healthy respect.
好的  孩子们
<i>All right, children,</i>
我们今天要学的第一段
<i>the first piece we're</i><i>going to learn today</i>
叫做“春之舞”
<i>is called</i><i>"a dance to spring."</i>
有谁想去便便
If anyone needs to make a doody,
请举手
please raise your hand.
爸爸
Daddy.
-不  亲爱的  我是说“便便”  -爸爸
-No, dear, I said "doody."   -Daddy.
派珀先生
Um, Mr. Piper.
嗨  我是艾米·邓肯  就是泰迪的妈妈
Hi, I'm Amy Duncan, Teddy's mom.
啊  泰迪·邓肯啊
Ah. Teddy Duncan.
她是我最...
She's one of my most...
的一个学生
Students.
是的  不管怎么说
Right. Anyway,
我想和你谈谈关于她上次的测验的事
I wanted to talk to you about her last quiz.
邓肯夫人  家长想找老师谈话
Mrs. Duncan, parents must schedule an appointment
是需要事先预约的
for <i>any</i> conference.
是的  我很抱歉
Right, and I am so sorry,
可是我是在午餐时间赶过来的
but I'm here now during my lunch hour,
所以你能不能破例一下
so if you could just make an exception.
让我查一查
Oh, let me check over here
适用于你的特殊条例
where I posted the special rules
贴在哪儿了
that apply only to you.
看  他们压根不存在
Oh, look, they don't exist.
不管怎样  你也看到了我的办公桌了
At any rate, as you can see by my desk,
我现在实在是太忙了
I am far too busy right now.
好吧
Oh, okay.
你现有的计划  熊妈妈已经帮你清空了
Mama bear just cleared your schedule.
盖比  帮我个忙...
Hey, Gabe, do me a favor...
听我说几句  然后谈谈你的看法
Listen to this and tell me what you think.
-你想说啥  -我要去和斯凯勒的前男友
-What is it?  -Well, I've gotta talk
谈一谈  告诉他不要再去打扰她了
to Skyler's ex-boyfriend and tell him to quit bothering her.
好吧  我认为你还是就此打住吧
Okay, let me stop you right there.
-快快快快  -什么意思
-Go go go go.  -What?
我只想让你别念了  我不感兴趣
Oh, I just wanted to stop you. I'm not interested.
这就是我想要说的
Okay, this is what I'm thinking about saying.
“你好  布洛克  你不认识我
"Hello, brock, you don't know me,"
但是我听说过很多关于你的事迹
but I've heard a lot of great things about you.
如果你不嫌麻烦的话
If it isn't too much trouble,
能不能请你别老给斯凯勒发短信了”
"could you please maybe stop texting Skyler so much?"
你到底是想臭骂他一顿还是想和他共舞赏花观月
Are you trying to tell him off or invite him to the prom?
和善的...  臭骂他一顿
Tell him off...  Nicely.
他就不会用拳头狠狠揍我一顿了
So he won't get all punchy and hurty on me.
你必须有点自信好不
Then you've gotta be confident!
-让他看看你是认真的  -噢  不
-Show him you mean business.  -Oh no.
-你在害怕什么  -这个啊  我怕小丑  怕蜘蛛  怕黑
-What are you afraid of?  -Well, clowns, spiders, the dark...
不  我是说你害怕什么布洛克的事
No, I mean with brock.
他是摔跤队的队长
He's the Captain of the wrestling team.
相信我...  所有的硬汉都本性难移
Trust me... all tough guys are the same.
你勇敢地面对他们  他们就会退让
You stand up to them, they'll always back down.
好吧  我...  我试试
All right, I'll... I'll try it.
-耶  -好的
-Yeah. Yeah.  -Okay.
布洛克
Brock.
我是PJ
This is P.J.
斯凯勒现在是我的女朋友
Skyler is my girlfriend now
我要求你以后别没事烦她
and I want you to stop bothering her.
啊  我没问题  好的  再见
Uh-huh. Works for me. Okay. Bye.
他要放学后见
He wants to meet after school.
-做什么  -我猜是家庭作业
-To do what?  -I'm guessing homework.
他说他要给我上一课（教训我）
He said he was gonna teach me a lesson.
嗨  你想见我  希伯特校长
Hi, you wanted to see me, principal hibbert?
是的  泰迪  请坐
Yes, Teddy, have a seat.
我想让你看些东西
I want to show you something
这是我们的监控录像今早些时候拍到的
our security cameras caught earlier today.
我想你会有兴趣的
I think you'll find it interesting.
我们能看看别的么
Can we see what else is on?
嘘嘘
Shh shh shh.
这个部分我最爱看
Here's my favorite part.
-为什么  为什么要快放  -那样更有趣
- Why... why is it in fast motion?  - It's funnier that way.
我  我不知道该说些什么
I... I don't know what to say.
对你来说喜忧参半
There's good news and bad news.
好消息是派珀先生同意了不对你母亲予以起诉
Mr. Piper has agreed not to press charges,
不过你妈妈以后别想踏入学校方圆百里之内
but your mother is banned from campus.
坏消息是什么
What's the bad news?
派珀先生申明需要一份道歉
Mr. Piper is demanding an apology.
哦  好的  好的
Oh. Oh, okay okay.
下次我见到他的时候我会向他说对不起的
Well, I'll say sorry to him the next time I see him.
他想听你家那位说
<i>Not</i> from you.
哦  坏消息来了
Ooh, there's the bad news.
嘿  亲爱的  查莉的第一堂芭蕾课怎么样
Hey, honey, how was Charlie's first ballet class?
好吧  听到这你肯定会气坏的
Okay, you're not gonna like this,
因为我在给查莉录影  所以她被踢出课堂了
but Charlie got kicked out of class because I was videotaping.
我会处理好的  所以请别对我大嚷大叫
But I'm gonna fix it, so please don't yell at me.
好吧
Okay.
要纸杯蛋糕么
Cupcake?
-纸杯蛋糕  -嗯
- Cupcake?  - Mm-hmm.
就这样  你不生气吗
That's it?You're not mad?
不  我不生气
No! I'm not mad.
亲爱的  我们这个家里大家
Honey, everybody in this family has to
都要学会宽以待人
learn to be very forgiving people.
你捅了什么篓子
What'd you do?
没什么
Nothing.
妈妈
<i>Mom!</i>
我想没什么的意思很快就要水落石出了
Ooh, I think we're gonna find out what "nothing" means.
怎么了  亲爱的
What's up, sweetie?
我刚在学校观赏了史上最有趣的无声电影
I just saw the most interesting nature film
-是吗  -今天  在学校  是关于
- Mmm?   - ...In school today. Yeah, it was about
暴走熊妈妈闯入学校疯狂追打老师
a mama bear that wandered into a classroom and chased a teacher.
很不错  亲爱的  要纸杯蛋糕吗
That's nice, dear. Cupcake?
不  不  纸杯蛋糕这招只有爸爸才会买账
No. No, cupcakes only work on dad.
大实话
It's true.
派珀先生明天晚上要过来
Mr. Piper is coming over tomorrow night
你必须得向他道歉
and you will apologize to him.
好的  我会道歉
Fine, I'll apologize.
我想当时我是有点失控了
I guess I got a little bit out of control.
我不知道我为什么那样做
I don't know why I do it.
有时我就是控制不住自己了
I just lose it sometimes.
你有看到我和他围着清洁工转悠那部分么
Did you see the part where I chased him around the janitor?
你得承认那还是有点好玩的  不是吗
You have to admit that was a little funny, right?
也许吧
Maybe a little.
唐娜小姐
Miss Donna?
-哦  邓肯先生  -哦
- Oh, Mr. Duncan.  - Oh!
嘿嘿  嗨
Hey hey. Hi. Huh.
唐娜小姐  你看  我刚刚只是
Miss Donna, you know, I was just...
展示芭蕾的标准屈膝动作
Demonstrating a well-executed plie.
你有学过芭蕾舞吗
You have some ballet experience?
哦  很久以前了  我不是...
Oh, it was a long time ago.I don't...
第一姿势
First position!
第二姿势
Second position.
亮相
Attitude.
现在来两个分腿跳
Now give me two grand jetes.
哦  不不不
Oh, no no no.
哦  好吧
Oh, all right.
跳得很不赖
Very impressive.
谢谢  谢谢  不过其实我
Thank you, thank you, but really I'm...
我之所以来这里
I'm here 'cause I'm hoping that
是希望你能重新让查莉上你的课
you'll let Charlie back in the dance class.
我会的  如果你能帮我个忙
Well, I will if you'll help me with something.
我在为芭蕾提高班排演芭蕾舞姿
I'm doing some choreography for one of my advanced classes.
我要做一个鹿跳  到你的胳膊上
Now I'm going to do a stag leap into your arms.
你把我举高
Lift me high
再把我轻轻地放到地面上
and then release me gently onto the floor.
这个  我  我只上过三节课啊
You know, I... I only had three classes.
哦  天哪
<i>Oh boy!</i>
唐娜小姐  你还好吧
Miss Donna, are you okay?
我的头陷到墙里了
My head's in a wall.
听着  关于查莉的事
Uh, listen, about the Charlie thing,
还有戏吗
how are we feeling?
-干嘛啊  -好吧  关于斯凯勒的前男友
- What's going on? - Okay, so I gave you a little bad advice
我之前给的建议不是很好  所以我要弥补下
about Skyler's old boyfriend and now I'm gonna make up for it.
你给我买了一个忍者吗
You bought me a ninja?
-小弟  -这是马特  我的空手道老师
- Dude. - This is Matt, my karate teacher.
-哦  嘿  -你还好吧
- Oh. Hey.  - How you doing?
哦
Oh!
马特让我成为了三年级最让人害怕的男孩
Matt's made me the most feared kid in the third grade.
-你是五年级  -嘿  一次一级
- You're in fifth grade.  - Hey, one grade at a time.
不管怎么说  马特会帮你赢下
Anyway, Matt's gonna help you win
-明天的那一仗  -好了  PJ
- your fight tomorrow.  - All right, P.J.,
让我看看你的能耐  攻击我  好吗
let's see what you've got. Come at me, all right?
我需要你出拳  打击  脚踢
I want you to punch, hit, kick.
我  我不想伤了你
I do... I don't want to hurt you.
那就是这件衣服的用处
That's the whole point of this suit.
你穿着这个  什么也感觉不到
You wearing this, can't feel a thing.
是吗  那么我有一个更好的想法
Really? Then I have a better idea.
-你还好吧  -你小子就是PJ啊
- How you doing?  - You P.J.?
你  等等  你是布洛克
Y... wait. You're brock,
摔跤队的队长
the Captain of the wrestling team?
教练说我是九十八磅重的愤怒的小鸟
My coach says I'm 98 lbs of white-hot fury.
这套衣服是怎么回事
What's with the outfit?
是自卫服
It's a self-defense suit.
对我来说正好
Fine by me.
哦  等等
Oh wait.
好了
Okay.
我们喝水休息一下
We'll take a water break.
不  等我把你教训完为止
No. Not until I'm done teaching you a lesson.
算了
Forget it.
我痛扁不了你  我不能让斯凯勒回心转意
I can't beat you up. I can't get Skyler back.
我不能穿紧身的牛仔裤  因为他们太宽松了
I can't wear skinny jeans 'cause they're too baggy.
伙计  我知道让你伤心很不爽
Man, I know it stinks to get your heart broken,
尤其是像斯凯勒那样又漂亮又聪明的
especially by someone as beautiful and smart as Skyler.
的确  漂亮
Well, beautiful.
可是你知道  打架从来解决不了问题
But you know, fighting never solved anything.
是的  我已经着手提高我的社交能力
Yeah, I've really gotta work on my people skills.
你会找到其他人的
You'll find someone else.
天涯何处无芳草
Plenty of fish in the sea.
我有点儿喜欢上另一个女孩了
Well, there is this one other girl I kinda have a crush on.
-谁  -泰迪·邓肯
- Who?  - Teddy Duncan.
你认识她
Do you know her?
老实说我还真认识
As a matter of fact, I do,
我刚好知道她现在单身
and I happen to know she is <i>totally</i> available.
哦  派珀先生来了
Oh, there's Mr. Piper.
现在  妈妈  你答应过你会好好表现的
Now, mom, you promised you'd be good.
熊妈妈已经金盆洗手了
Mama bear has been declawed.
-开门  -开始了
- Open the door.  - Here we go.
啊  派珀先生  请进
Ah. Mr. Piper, come on in.
很好  你记得我妈妈吗
Ah. Wonderful. You remember my mom?
闭上眼睛全是她
Every time I close my eyes.
妈妈
Mom.
你不是有话要对派珀先生说吗
Wasn't there something you wanted to say to Mr. Piper?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
哪里错了
For?
把你桌子上的东西都扫到地上
Swiping everything off your desk.
-还有  -在走廊里追你
- And? - Chasing you through the hallway.
-还有  -你像小女生一样尖叫
- While?  - You screamed like a little girl.
好的
Okay!
可以了  好了  有谁饿了吗
Good enough. All right, who's hungry?
哦  爸爸  你回来了
Oh, dad, there you are.
老妈  你何不先闭上嘴巴
Mom, why don't you go check on dinner
去看看晚饭如何了
without saying anything else?
-鲍伯·邓肯  -皮特·派珀（儿歌里的名字)
- Bob Duncan.  - Peter Piper.
-你在开玩笑  是吗  -不  他没开玩笑  从来没有 永远不会
- You're kidding, right? - No, he's not kidding. Never has, never will.
那么  鲍伯  你是做什么工作的
So, Bob, what do you do for a living?
我是除虫专家
I'm an exterminator.
真好笑  你整天都在消灭害虫
The irony. You spend all day getting rid of pests,
回家以后却得面对害虫之王
then you come home to the biggest one of all.
要蔬菜沙拉吗
Crudites?
-你在说我妻子  -蔬菜沙拉
- You talking about my wife?  - Crudites?
你知道  皮特·派珀
You know, Peter Piper,
现在拿上你的腌辣椒
you're gonna be picking your pickled peppers
-滚到你的另一边...  -爸爸
- out of the other side of your... - Dad!
-你在威胁我吗  -哦  这只是开胃菜  伙计
- Are you threatening me?  - Oh, this is just the appetizers, people.
我们都消消气
Let's pace ourselves.
赶快道歉
Just say you're sorry.
好吧
All right.
我很难过你和一个疯子结婚了
I'm sorry you married a lunatic.
你死定了
That's it.
不  又开始了
Oh no! It's happening again!
迷你乳蛋饼
Mini quiche?
嘿  回来  你这狡猾的家伙
Hey! Come back here, you little weasel!
你比你的妻子还疯狂
You're crazier than your wife!
嘿  没有人比我妻子还疯狂
Hey! No one's crazier than my wife!
是的  没人比我还疯狂
Yeah! No one's crazier than me!
课上见
See you in class!
嗨  达布尼太太
Hi, Mrs. dabney.
嘿  查莉  我们在你的第一次芭蕾舞表演会上
Hey, Charlie. So we're here at your very first ballet recital
我要把它全都录下来
and I'm gonna get the whole thing on tape.
哦
Ooh.
真奇怪
That's odd.
有一个叫布洛克的家伙约我出去
Some guy named brock just asked me out.
我很好奇他是谁
I wonder who he is.
不知道
No idea.
哦  开始了
Ooh, it's starting.
欢迎大家
Welcome, everyone,
来到唐娜小姐的舞蹈学校
to miss Donna's school of dance.
在这次表演中  唐娜小姐的角色将由
In this performance, the role of miss Donna
鲍伯·邓肯来扮演
will be played by Bob Duncan.
哇哦
Whoo!
不多说了
Without further ado,
一朵花开了
a flower is born.
嘿嘿
Hey! Hey!
嘿嘿嘿
Hey hey hey hey hey!
好了  我是一朵很友好的花  我是一朵很友好的花
Come on, I'm a friendly flower. I'm a friendly flow...
嘿  我很友好
Hey! I'm friendly!
别跑
Don't run!
-这表演可真短啊  -太棒了
- That was a very short recital.  - It was awesome!
就像一场怪兽电影
It was like a monster movie.
我  我说这里不许录像
I... I said no videotaping in here.
我得赶紧说了  好运  查莉
Well, I just have to say really quick... good luck, Charlie!
好了  准备好了吗
Okay, are you ready?
我不知道  爸爸
I don't know, dad.
泰迪  你能相信我吗  我知道我在做什么
Teddy, would you trust me? I know what I'm doing.
这话似曾相识
Heard those words before.
这次
Well, this time...
这次我是认真的
This time I mean it.
好的  我们开始
All right, here we go.
天哪  真该好好练练技术了
Man! I gotta work on my technique.
难道不是吗
Ya think?